uh good morning church happy
Sabbath let us uh pause for a word of
prayer bow your heads with me
please heavenly
father I want to thank you Lord for your
mercy I want to thank you Lord for the
message you have for us this
morning Lord help us to be ready for
your
coming your soon coming is our prayer in
Jesus name
amen so
um this
morning I
am both excited and
nervous because I have something very
important to tell
you and now I have your
attention
um this is so important I believe it's
going to
change um the way that you live your
life and
um I it's so important I can't even tell
you the name of the sermon right now
because it would just scare you well
maybe it might make you happy hopefully
it would make you happy but it would
definitely make you look at me
funny so I'm not telling you the name of
the sermon right now
what I will ask you is
this how many of you would live life
differently if you thought that Jesus
was returning really really really
soon what do you think do you think
there's some things you might change uh
maybe in the way you're doing things
right now or the way that you relate to
people um maybe your priorities do you
think that might happen if we knew Jesus
was coming back let's say before the end
of this
year you know there's a lot of talk
going on about different things
happening you know natural disasters and
we know that a very special visit is
happening here um in the United States
of America by the pope to address our
government and things uh uh are really
really uh happening rapidly what would
you do if you knew that Jesus was coming
back before the end of this year if I
were to ask you right now hey you know
what turn to your neighbor and just say
hey you know tell them what would you
different what would you do differently
I mean I think there might be some
discussion you know right now uh my
family is going through this you know my
husband my wife we're we're going
through this thing my kids we're going
through this and and you know if if I
knew that Jesus was coming back before
the end of the year I would probably
like give up some things in in my life I
would probably start to uh prioritize
some things that I was not uh
prioritizing uh prior to this I would
change some things in my
life
well I want to share with
you that uh I believe that there is
evidence that Jesus is coming
soon and that's the easy part amen
praise the Lord but I believe that there
is evidence that Jesus is coming before
the end of the
year I know I know you're probably
wondering what am I going to say to
Pastor on the way out of the door after
this
sermon um but I believe that there is
evidence that Jesus is indeed coming
before the end of the year and I'm going
to take you on a scriptural Journey this
morning to show you based on Bible
evidence solid Bible evidence that Jesus
is coming before the end of the year now
before you pull out your phones and
start texting
people and before you start thinking
about see I told you he was a heretic
before you do that
please allow me to take you through the
scriptures is that okay
by the way I'm not setting a
date I want you to turn with me to the
Book of
Exodus Exodus chapter 12 what would you
do if you knew that Jesus was coming if
he was coming in your lifetime if he was
coming very soon and in fact if he was
coming sooner than you thought I believe
beloved that Jesus is coming and he's
coming very soon in the book of Exodus
chapter 12 uh we pick up with a story of
of the children of Israel and they are
uh in uh captivity uh to the Egyptians
and God is about to do something amazing
he is about to deliver the children of
Israel from captivity and so we read
beginning with Exodus 12 verse 1 the
Bible says here and the Lord spake unto
Moses and Aaron in the land of Egypt
saying this month shall be the beginning
the be shall be unto you the beginning
of months it shall be the first month of
the year to you speaky unto all the
congregation of Israel saying in the
10th day of this month they shall take
to them every man a lamb according to
the house of their fathers a lamb for a
house and if the house will be too small
for the lamb let him and his neighbor
next unto his house take it according to
the number of souls every man according
to his eating you shall make shall make
your account for the lamb and your lamb
shall be without blemish a male of the
first year he shall take it out from the
sheep or from the goats and he shall
keep it up until the 14th day of the
same month and the whole assembly of the
congregation of Israel shall kill it in
the evening and they shall take of the
blood and strike it on the two side post
on the upper door post of the house
wherein they
eat in verse 18 in the first month of
the 14th 14th day of the month at even
you shall eat unleavened bread until the
one and 20th day of the month at
even so what's going on
here I see some of you looking at me
real troubled right now
listen the children of Israel being in
Egyptian captivity were about to be
delivered and God instructs them he says
I want you to take take a lamb and
sacrifice that lamb and when you
sacrifice that lamb I want you to take
the blood and put it on the doorpost of
the house and it will signify your
deliverance I will pass over you amen
and so and so he says Listen by the way
when you do this and I deliver you out
of captivity I'm going to give you
something special I'm going to give you
a calendar
now how many of you notice that God
tells Moses this month will be the first
month for you did you see that so so God
is telling the children of Israel that
your deliverance from captivity is going
to Mark a new year you are going to not
operate on the calendar of the Egyptians
I am giving you my own
calendar and that calendar
begins with the Passover you with me so
far yeah so
God instructs the children of Israel he
says this month let's read it again
verse one or verse
two uh this month shall be unto you the
beginning of months it shall be the
first month of the what of the Year to
you it shall be the first month of the
year to
you well that's very interesting because
this year then would not be an Egyptian
year it would be God's year are you with
me so far God's year so so we might call
this year God's year or the year of God
why because God was instituting a
calendar that he himself would be in
charge of and within that year we're
going to find various events in other
words the year began with Passover which
was a feast but there were several other
feasts in fact there were seven feasts
in in all that made up the Jewish year
if you're with me so far just say Amen
now let's look at what those feasts were
by the way let me share something with
you very quickly here just to just to I
want to uh uh have you see something if
you notice again with me in fact let's
go over to Leviticus 23 and verse4
Leviticus chap
23 and verse
4 L
23:4 the Bible says these are the feasts
of the Lord even holy convocation which
ye shall Proclaim in their what seasons
in their Seasons now the Hebrew word
that is used here is the word moed and
it actually means time or year so God is
saying here to the children of Israel
these are the seasons that you shall
Proclaim in their what everyone year now
let me share something with you uh if
you were to turn to Daniel 12 and: 7 uh
there the Bible describes a specific
time period And it describes it simply
by the term time times and half a time
now what is a
time it's a year guess what the same
Hebrew word moed that is used in
Leviticus 23 is the same Hebrew word
used in Daniel 12:7 talking about time
time times and half a time which we
understand to be a year so God is saying
to the children of Israel these are the
feasts that will make up your year if
you're with me so far just say amen amen
now let's see what these feasts were uh
if we read verse four verse 5 in the
14th day of the first month of uh first
first month at even is the Lord's what
Passover verse six and on the 15th day
of the same month is the Feast of
unleavened bread unto the Lord seven
days you must eat on leaven bread then
jump down with me to verse n and the
Lord spake unto Moses saying Speak unto
the children of Israel and say unto them
when you be come into the land which I
give you you shall reap the Harvest
thereof then you shall and you shall
reap the Harvest thereof then shall ye
bring a sheath of the first fruits of
your Harvest unto the priest and he
shall wave the sheath before the Lord to
be accepted for you on the tomorrow
after the Sabbath the priest shall wed
so let me explain what's going on here
God gives out three feasts they are the
Passover the very next day was a feast
of unleavened bread and this Feast
you'll remember the children of Israel
were to put leaven out of their house
right signifying a removal of sin okay
so Passover and and then unleavened
bread and then the very next day was the
Feast of first fruits amen yeah and the
first fruits was a celebration of a
harvest now want you to notice with me
uh verse let's see here
verse
15 and you shall count on unto you from
the tomorrow after the Sabbath from the
day that you brought the sheath of the
wave offering seven Sabbath shall be
complete even unto tomorrow after the
seventh Sabbath shall you number 50 days
and you shall offer a new meat offering
unto the Lord
so uh we have here uh the Feast of
Pentecost which was to occur how many
days 50 days right after the Feast of
first fruits so you have Pentecost these
were four feast days that made up the
Jewish year now if you read further down
in the book in The Book of Leviticus you
will see that there were three feasts
following uh there was the Feast of
trumpets anyone ever heard of that Feast
yeah the Feast of trumpets and the Feast
of trumpets was an announcement that
judgment was coming after the Feast of
trumpets was the day of
atonement and on the day of atonement it
signified judgment and then the last
Feast of the Jewish year was the Feast
of Tabernacle Les and that was that
Feast of Tabernacles represented a
celebration of all that God had done for
his people throughout the
year these are the feasts of the Lord
let me say this way this was the year of
the Lord the what everyone the year of
the Lord one more time n this was the
year of the Lord now why do we need to
understand this and why why is this so
important for us to grasp I will share
with you go with me to the Book of John
1 verse
29 John 1 verse 29 now that verse may
already ring a bell to you and sound
familiar uh in the context of this verse
John the Baptist has just seen Jesus and
when he sees him he identifies him in a
very special way notice what he says in
John 1:29 the next day John seeth J
Jesus coming unto him and saith
Behold the Lamb of God which taketh away
the sin of the
world I am so excited right now you may
not know why but you will know why
soon John sees Jesus and he says look
here is the Lamb of God which takes away
the sin of the world
now that might not sound significant to
you in the context of what we're talking
about but now remember what happens
after this is Jesus is baptized he goes
to the Wilderness where he's tempted
three times and then he returns from the
Wilderness so let's go over to the Book
of Luke chapter 4 Luke chapter
4 and uh please notice with me Luke
chapter 4 you'll notice verses 1 through
13 it's all about the Temptation right
Jesus being tempted in the wilderness
and him overcoming the devil right
that's what happens in verse 1-13 now
notice with me verse
14 and Jesus returned in the power of
the spirit into Galilee and there went
out of Fame of of him throughout all the
region round about and he taught all in
their synagogues being glorified of all
and he came to Nazareth where he had
been brought up and as his custom was he
went into the synagogue on the Sabbath
day and stood up for to read and there
was delivered unto him the book of the
prophet Isaiah and when he had opened
the book he found the place where it was
written all right so stop don't read any
further stop don't read any further look
up at me stop you're stop don't look up
at me look look at the ground look
somewhere else don't look at the screens
stop Jesus has been identified as the
Lamb of God
he goes into the Wilderness overcomes
the devil and then when he returns he
goes to Nazareth and they he goes into
into the synagogue and they give him the
books to read and he finds the place in
the book of Isaiah where it says now
listen carefully the
spirit you can go there
now is it up there okay here we go the
spirit of the Lord is upon me because he
has anointed me to preach the gospel to
the poor he has sent me to heal the
brokenhearted to preach Deliverance to
the captives and recovering of sight to
the blind to set at Liberty them that
are
bruised and
then and
then to
preach the
acceptable what year of the to preach
what the acceptable year of the Lord
what is that what's he talking about
what is he talking about God has sent me
to preach the acceptable year of the
Lord and then check out what he does
after that let's go to the next verse
verse 20 it says and he closed the book
and gave it again to the minister and
sat down and the eyes of them all were
in the were in the synagogue were
fastened on him verse
21 and he began to say unto them this
day is this scripture fulfilled in your
ears
wait
what how is the how is this scripture
how is the year of the Lord this day
being fulfilled in your ears what is he
talking
about I want to show you something else
interesting go with me to the Book of
Mark chapter
1 Mark chapter 1
and notice with me verse
15 Mark chapter 1 once again if you
notice up in verse 12 and 13 you'll see
that Jesus has just come out of the
Wilderness verse 14 now after that John
was put in prison Jesus came into
Galilee preaching what the gospel of the
kingdom of God so Matthew 4 uh Luke 4
says he was going to preach the
acceptable year of the Lord uh Matthew
says he's preaching the
kingdom of God the gospel of the kingdom
of God and now notice this verse 15
saying here's what he's saying the time
is
fulfilled the what
time the the what time now what is time
now this is Greek okay so let me just
show you it's not the same Hebrew word
that was used back in Daniel chapter uh
12 or in the Book of Leviticus this is
Greek but let me share something with
you the same Greek word that is used
here is the same Greek word that is used
in Revelation 12 that tells us that the
woman went into the Wilderness where she
was hiding for a time times and half a
Time same Greek word what is a time a
year so Jesus is saying that I'm telling
you he begins to preach that the year of
the Lord is
here what do you you mean
listen
listen remember in the Old Testament you
had these seven feasts right and the the
the feast the first Feast was
what Passover Passover
began the year of the
Lord what was Passover about
a
lamb being
sacrificed to provide Deliverance for
the
people and so this event began the year
of the
Lord now every year the Year of the Lord
occurred yeah but but the year of the
Lord was really an object lesson to
point to something greater
yes it was pointing to the fact that
soon one would come who would be the
true Lamb of God Amen and when that lamb
came guess what what would
begin so if the year of the Lord began
with the lamb being
sacrificed and it
ended with the day of atonement and then
a celebration Feast of Tabernacles a
celebration of what God had done for his
people then the end of the year would be
whatever time that is that the day of
atonement occurs and everything is
wrapped up and we are celebrating what
God has done for us
previously yeah so what is that telling
us guys
that from the time Christ came to this
earth as the Lamb of God that event
began the acceptable year of the Lord
and that year the real year remember
before it was just a type every year
they would go through this example okay
this is what's going to happen when the
Messiah comes and these are the the
events that are going to follow and this
is what the feast days are teaching us
but when Christ comes reality meets
Shadow the true year of the Lord begins
and it begins that's why Jesus says I've
come to preach the acceptable year of
the Lord which beloved is the reason we
can know without a shadow of a doubt
that Jesus is coming before the end of
the
year I know you were
nervous and you need to be nervous
relax calm down your pastor's not crazy
guys okay Jesus is coming by the end of
the year if you're with me just say Amen
you get the picture he is coming at the
end of the year no not this year at the
end of the
year but Beloved the point I'm trying to
illustrate to you is that guess what we
are at the end of the
year no no no no no no no no we're not
in the beginning of the year we are at
the end of the year time is short it
really really is think of it like this
in heaven
time Jesus has only been gone for a
year you see beloved to us we're human
we're you know we're these little things
in the universe and so for us time is
just like Whoa We have been here for how
long now it's been this many thousands
of of years but in heaven Beloved the
Angels like you know what this is just
we're just going through a year it's a
year in Heavenly
Time and so beloved while we're on Earth
thinking oh yeah we got a lot of time no
beloved I want you to see just how close
to the end we really are Jesus is coming
before the end of the year and we are
living in the end
of the year you say Pastor please
explain to me further well listen Christ
was the Passover Lamb just like in the
type Christ his death set Humanity who
chose to accept him set them free from
sins amen and then the next Feast was
the unleavened bread signifying a
putting away of sin just as Christ's
death put away sin amen and then the
first fruits the third Feast which
happened on the third day was a symbol
of of of of a a celebration of a harvest
well guess what when Jesus resurrects
from the grave there are people who come
up out of the Grave with him symbolizing
a harvest so
look Jesus kicks off the year of the
Lord with the Passover his death Le
unleavened bread his burial the Feast of
first fruits his
resurrection yeah and then we know that
50 days Days Later came the Feast of
Pentecost which was another celebration
of another Harvest and guess what on the
day of Pentecost in Acts chapter 2 we
have the spirit of God being poured out
by the way how many rains are they are
there in the
year how many Reigns are there in the
Jewish year
two I try on this side two the early
rain and the latter rain yeah so there
only two rains in the year there's the
early rain there's the latter rain
beloved it symbolizes a whole unit a
whole year so we know that on the day of
Pentecost it symbolized the early rain
and we know that the latter rain will
take place at the End of Time simply
meaning that this whole time period from
Jesus's death burial and Resurrection to
the second coming has only
been one
year we are
waiting for the latter rain yes we are
waiting for that final outpouring of
God's spirit because Jesus is coming
soon for the
Harvest and the Harvest evidently takes
place at the
end of the
year in
fact Jesus himself said the Harvest is
the end of the
world yeah and the end of the world is
synonymous with the end of the
year so Christ is trying to get us ready
for that grand Harvest he's trying to
get us prepared and if you knew that
Jesus was coming back before the end of
the year how much would you change about
what you're doing
now how many people would you seek to
make peace with that you have not made
peace with how many relationships would
you try to restore if you knew that
Jesus was coming back before the end of
the year how much would your mindset
change how many prayer meetings would
you be
at if you knew that Jesus was
coming before the end of the
year yeah how many how many nights of
Evangelistic meetings
how much would we do
differently how much more would we be
reaching out to our neighbors and our
friends if we knew that Jesus was coming
back before the end of the
year Well beloved I'm telling you with
the absolute confidence of everything I
can muster up to you Jesus is coming
before the end of the year
and we are currently living in the end
of the year and if that is the case
beloved it's time for us to put away our
foolishness it's time for us to put away
our biggering it's time for us beloved
to be on one page and you know what I
didn't want to preach this because I'm
saving it for another sermon but I have
to preach it because I came up in
Sabbath school this morning
if
animals Sabbath
school if animals on an
ark could live together in
harmony because of the spirit of God
within that Ark how dare we as human
beings within the Church of God have
issues with one
another how can animals be better
how can animals be an ex in fact God you
know the wicked are stand and they're
watching the animals walk onto the ark
clean and
unclean dwelling
together Lions not tearing each other up
lamb and lion laying down together how
can animals live in peace when sometimes
you and I can't but if we knew that
Jesus was coming again before the end of
the year how much more would we be
striving to make peace in our
homes peace in our
relationships beloved I'm going to ask
you a question now you if I asked you
this before and I said H if I asked you
this before probably none of you would
raise your hands because you'd be like
no Pastor you are the only crazy one in
here today but now I'm going to ask it
how many of you believe Jesus is coming
before the end of the year
yeah and if you believe that ought we
not to live as though we believe it
ought we not to start behaving as though
we believe that Christ truly is coming
before the end of the year ought we not
to be telling people you don't
understand Jesus is coming and he's
coming you may not want to say before
the end of the year I get that but you
could just say he's coming really really
really really really soon unless you set
the context and show them what the year
of the Lord
is but beloved we have to be about our
father's
business so listen turn with me to the
Book of Numbers 32 numbers 32 and as
you're turning there you we stopped at
the at the Feast of Pentecost we know
that a few months passed before the
Feast of trumpets was sounded and the
Feast of trumpets was a warning that
judgment was coming and we know that
according to Daniel 8: 13 and 14 that
the Judgment began in 1844 which beloved
all I'm trying to say is that as of 1844
we have been in the time of the end
actually a little bit before that we
have been in the time of the
end the end of
what the end of the
year that's the time we are living in
right now it is the time of the end or
the end of the year and I love this
beloved because listen in Daniel chap 11
11: 40 the Bible says and at the time of
the end the King of the North and the
King of the South are going to be
engaged in Conflict I'm not going to get
into the detail of that right now I'm
simply saying this that in Daniel 11:40
it talks about the time of the end and
then it said something very special it
says that this King of the North which
is symbolic of the
papacy is going to hear some
news out of the North and out of the
East Tidings the Bible says out of the
North and out of the East that's going
to trouble him and cause him to try to
destroy many and who are those many it's
God's people so the question is what is
the message or the tidings that the King
of the North the papacy hears at the
time of the end or toward the end of the
year that angers him and makes him want
to go and Destroy many listen carefully
according to Revelation CH 7 the bible
says I saw an angel ascending from the
east from the where everyone the East
having the Seal of the Living God
Beloved the sealing message The Three
Angels messages of Revelation chapter 14
is the are is the tidings from the East
that trouble the King of the North what
am I saying to you if it is the time of
the end which it is then you and I need
to be
preaching these
Tidings it is time for you and I to grab
a hold of this message and preach it
with power and conviction because when
we start preaching with power and
conviction that is what angers the King
of the North and before there is any
preaching with power and conviction the
King of the North is not going to be
angry the Bible says it
so you have no reason to be running from
the King of the North if you're not
preaching the
gospel cuz he's not going to be angry
with
you the anger comes when the word of God
is being preached so powerfully that
thousands are being drawn out of the
reach of
deception
listen numbers
32 numbers 32
I want you to
notice verse one we're getting ready to
close numbers
32 and verse
one now the children of Reuben and the
children of GAD had a very G multi a
very great multitude of what cattle and
when they saw the land of jar and the
land of Gilead that behold the place was
a place for cattle the children of God
and the children of the children of GAD
and the children of Reuben came and
spake unto Moses and to Eleazar the
priest and onto the princes of the
congregation saying adth and and and de
and and Debon and jazar and Nimar nimra
and hesban and ilot man these names
verse four even the country which the
Lord smote before the congregation of
Israel is a land for cattle and thy
servants have cattle wherefore said they
if we have found Grace in thy sight let
this land be given unto thy servants for
a possession and bring us not over the
Jordan the children of Israel
were going over to the
Jordan to do battle to do what everyone
battle but two of the tribes saw that
the land was good
for for
what
for
cattle so we have two scenarios before
us one preparing for battle the other
preparing for
cattle
battle
Cattle two tribes were were concerned
about their cattle their livelihood
their you know this is how we this is
our livelihood
the other tribes were going to
battle two tribes were were were more
concerned with making a
living in a time of battle in a time
where where the Brethren needed each
other two tribes wanted to take care of
their
cattle and so uh uh Moses responds unto
the children of GAD and to the children
of Reuben shall your brethren go to
battle while you sit here and
cattle shall your brethren go out to
battle look next verse next verse verse
7 and wherefore discourage ye the heart
of the children of Israel from going
over into the land which the Lord has
given them thus did your fathers when I
sent them from cadesh Baria to to see
the
land you see beloved what was happening
back then is that the people became more
concerned with their livelihood than
with the work of the Lord how many of us
today are
cattling while our Brethren are
battling yeah you're going to do what
you're going to hold a oh you're going
to do what you're going to go oh yeah
you know what I I
would I really
would I would I would but
beloved I'm not trying to make you feel
bad yes I
am no I'm not I'm not trying to make you
feel feel bad I'm just saying
listen the Lord is coming he's coming
before the end of the year so if he's
coming before the end of the year the
Year just in case you forgot the
year if he's coming before the end of
the year then then we ought to be in
battle mode not cattle mode if there was
any time to be in cattle mode it may
have been at the beginning of the year
and maybe even at the middle of the year
not really but if there was a time to be
in cattle mode yeah but but now is time
for battle there there is no time for
cattle I'm not saying not to take care
of yourself and and and livelihood no no
no that's not what I'm saying but I'm
saying that the Prime Focus of the
Christian today must be that the Lord is
coming before the end of the year and
I've got to be in battle mode
shall I cattle while my brethren battle
God forbid God forbid and I like how how
how this story ends we'll just read it
very quickly numbers
32:16 it says uh and they came near unto
him and said we will build sheep fulls
for our cattle and cities for our little
ones we're going to take care of our
livelihood but we ourselves will go
ready armed before the children of
Israel until we have brought them unto
their place and our little ones shall
dwell in the fence cities because of the
inhabitants of the land we will not
return unto our houses until the
children of Israel have inherited every
man his
inheritance in other words they said
listen we our cattle are important to us
but you know what we are going with you
to
fight beloved you do you know the you
know the shocking Church rule right 20%
of the
people battle
while 80% of the
People
Cattle huh is is that
right yeah is it is it the rule 20% of
the people do all do 80% of the
work and 8% of the people do 20% of the
work look you know what want you to do
this for me say we love you Pastor
Myers that was weak and only this
section right here said it so let's try
it again we love you Pastor Myers love
you
I love you guys too it's so nice of you
to say those
things but Beloved the Bible says whom
God loves he chastens yeah whom he loves
he rebukes listen it's not that I'm not
doing any re I'm just telling you what
the word of God says and all I'm saying
is
listen don't hide behind
cattle take care of your cattle but
don't hide behind it to do the work of
the Lord time is wrapping up I want to
make a simple
appeal this appeal is going to be a
tough
appeal this appeal is not this appeal is
for those of you who have been
cattling and today you're saying Lord
enough I I'm joining the battle I'm
joining the battle
uh I will be there short of you know the
heavens falling I will be there when we
hold an Evangelistic meeting I will be
there at prayer meeting I will be I will
come to Sabbath
school I'll take those three amens right
there I'll take those I'll work with
that yeah I know I know it's hard
because you're thinking man you know
what I cattle so much throughout the
week that I get up on Sabbath morning
and I'm tired but you know what guys
your brethren need to see your fa listen
you know how discouraging it is and I've
been there to hold an Evangelistic
meeting and see more
visitors than church
members I mean if visitors come and they
look around and the church members by
their absence are saying this message is
yeah I mean they what they read is this
if this message was so important where
are all the
members and if you don't shake my hand
as you walk out the door and walk out
one of those doors I'll know
[Laughter]
why but beloved think about what we're
saying to the world think about what
we're saying to our visitors if they
come to a prayer meeting if they come to
an Evangelistic meeting if they come to
Sabbath school yay if they come to
church and our absence speaks louder
than anything we have to say
so look you you know your Arrangements
you know what's going on in your life
and I'm not listen I understand things
happen we we live complicated lives so
please don't get mad at me all I'm
saying is that we ought to be doing our
best is that fair we ought to be doing
our best to support the cause to help
the Brethren and in fact while I'm on it
your your
dollars God needs your dollars for
battle not that he need your dollars but
your dollars help with the battle and
when we divert our dollars to just deal
with our cattle and don't support God's
battle yes that's a plug for
tithing it's a plug for offering
supporting this church with your
offerings supporting this Mission with
your offerings because remember you're
not supporting me the pastor you're
supporting the
message that's what you your tithing
shows I believe in this message so the
church could be correct the church could
be doing all kinds of crazy things but
your tithe dollar is supporting the
mission not an
individual so my appeal I'm closing my
Bible
see my
appeal this is very
simple I've been
cattling I've been cattling and today I
join the battle
today I join the battle I want to be
ready when Jesus comes again and today I
join the battle so I'm going to do
something I haven't done I don't think
I've done before I'm going to ask for
those of you who are making a decision
today to stop
cattling to stop having your focus being
cattling and to start having be being
battling I'm going to ask would you be
willing to stand and come down to the
front if I listen and pause pause if you
are batt in and I see you come down here
I'm going to send you back to your
seat don't just get up for the exercise
this is not for exercise okay hey feel
like taking a walk I'm tired no this is
for those of you and so if there's only
one let there be only one but if there's
10 or 20 then praise God let there be 10
and 20 so you have been cattling you
saying Lord today I'm deciding to battle
if that's you I want to ask would you
stand to your feet and
come would you stand to your feet and
come
today I start the battle today you are
going to be able to count on me to do
something I'm not sure what it is but
you're going to be able to count on me
praise the Lord praise the
Lord praise the
Lord come on that's you I'm talking to
you who usually do not get up for the
appeal right you who usually do not
you're not found have please please
please listen to the message that I just
shared Jesus is going to be here before
the end of the year what are you waiting
for All Hands need to be on
deck All Hands need to be on deck listen
we need you this church needs you right
now there are we have positions that
need to be filled and we have a only few
people we can call we need your help in
so many many different ways why because
Jesus is coming again and he's coming
again soon he's coming again soon praise
God praise God for you who have come
down to join the battle to join the
battle and now my second appeal and if
you want to stand stand just stand where
you are for this appeal I want to be
ready because I believe that Jesus is
coming back before the end of the year
if that's your desire to be ready to
meet Jesus I want to invite you to
stand Heavenly
Father what a message you have given us
in this year of the
Lord you have shown us Lord that we can
know without a shadow of a doubt and
without time setting that Jesus is
indeed coming back before the end of the
year not 2015 or 16 or 17 we don't know
that we believe you're coming soon but
we know one thing for
sure that you are coming before the end
of that prophetic
year of the
scripture and so father we know that we
are living at the very end of the year
and we are asking Lord that you would
help us especially in this time to not
be so focused on cattling that we
neglect to battle
help us Lord to strengthen the hands of
our Brethren by being present in the
battle and father especially for those
who who have come down to the front to
officially join the battle I pray that
you would Inspire them that you would
put your spirit within their hearts to
tell them how they can be of assistance
to this battle what positions they can
fill for this battle and father I want
to pray especially I want to pray
especially tonight that we will show up
for
battle I I don't know Lord people have
things we know Sabbath plans but Lord
might tonight be a message of the
effectiveness of this
message may we put
aside everything else
Lord and begin to put you first in our
lives and father we thank you because
this church is growing but father we
want it to grow more we want it to grow
faster we thank you for the work that
has been being done in previous years
and we thank you for the work that you
are going to do in the Years coming
up bless us Lord as we prepare for
battle in Jesus name we pray amen you
may be seated